[
     {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (4x + 7) + (7x + 4)?",
      "correctAnswer": "11x + 11",
      "options": [
        "11x + 12",
        "10x + 11",
        "11x + 11",
        "12x + 11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (7x + 3) + (3x + 7)?",
      "correctAnswer": "10x + 10",
      "options": [
        "10x + 10",
        "9x + 10",
        "10x + 11",
        "11x + 10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (10x + 8) + (8x + 10)?",
      "correctAnswer": "18x + 18",
      "options": [
        "18x + 19",
        "19x + 18",
        "18x + 18",
        "17x + 18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (8x + 7) + (7x + 8)?",
      "correctAnswer": "15x + 15",
      "options": [
        "14x + 15",
        "15x + 15",
        "16x + 15",
        "15x + 16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (1x + 10) + (10x + 1)?",
      "correctAnswer": "11x + 11",
      "options": [
        "11x + 11",
        "12x + 11",
        "10x + 11",
        "11x + 12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (6x + 4) + (4x + 6)?",
      "correctAnswer": "10x + 10",
      "options": [
        "9x + 10",
        "10x + 10",
        "10x + 11",
        "11x + 10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (3x + 9) + (9x + 3)?",
      "correctAnswer": "12x + 12",
      "options": [
        "13x + 12",
        "12x + 13",
        "11x + 12",
        "12x + 12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (4x + 5) + (5x + 4)?",
      "correctAnswer": "9x + 9",
      "options": [
        "9x + 10",
        "10x + 9",
        "9x + 9",
        "8x + 9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (5x + 3) + (3x + 5)?",
      "correctAnswer": "8x + 8",
      "options": [
        "9x + 8",
        "8x + 8",
        "8x + 9",
        "7x + 8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (10x + 8) + (8x + 10)?",
      "correctAnswer": "18x + 18",
      "options": [
        "17x + 18",
        "18x + 18",
        "18x + 19",
        "19x + 18"
      ]
    }
]